start sharing your
journey we are all struggling and trying
to find the light at the end of the
tunnel the end of the day that's what is
happening right so you have an
opportunity to start becoming that light
even in your pain I know this sounds
hard or it might be difficult but you
can do it with a little bit of light
just a little bit right it's there's a
saying I think it was in a song that you
just need a little crack in your window
for the light to come in it doesn't
doesn't have to be fully open just a
little crack and so that's something
that I want to start off with I want you
guys to just consider that in your
journey right now because a lot of the
calls I've gotten is I'm in pain and I
need a solution today I'm in pain I
don't want to tell my wife until I'm
fixed it's like well why would you do
that if if your wife is a confidant if
your wife is a partner then you're part
of your healing
is to share your journey right now part
of it is being vulnerable in this moment
and being able to tell them hey this is
what I'm going through because let me
tell you a secret there may be something
that she's going through and she's held
as well because she was too afraid to
tell you like just imagine what kind of
relationship you're building when you go
there first when your honesty is the
pathway for something to change right
like me and my wife that's one of our
biggest gifts is we are so transparent
with each other The Good the Bad the
Ugly right and it's been like that since
my journey when we didn't know what was
going on with me she knew that I
couldn't have sex I I didn't know why I
just it it wasn't working and because I
had such an amazing partner she said we
will figure it out together it was a we
right and so this community for those
listening right now this is your we we
are in this together right now so when
this call is done get on the Facebook
group and start sharing your journey get
on the Facebook group and if you're
already ahead of someone start helping
others in their Journey right that's how
we start getting better this is not like
well I don't know I can't do anything
right now you can like Dr Steven DeVos
you started this many many years ago he
didn't know how big it's going to get he
didn't know who's going to follow him he
didn't know that this community is going
to get so big he just started putting
things out to help others now here we
are my last one that I did had 15,000
view some of his views are in hundreds
thousands like it's that's how you start
you start with the first step